import Plug from "./plugSVG.svg";
import Attic from "./atticSVG.svg";
import Basement from "./basementSVG.svg";
import Drainage from "./drainageSVG.svg";
import Gutter from "./gutterSVG.svg";
import HeatCool from "./heatcoolSVG.svg";
import Plumb from "./plumbSVG.svg";
import Roof from "./roofSVG.svg";
import Wall from "./wallImg.svg";
import Wind from "./winDoorSVG.svg";

export var servicesCard = [
  {
    image: Plug,
    textFront: "Electrical Panels & Breakers",
    textBack: "We assess the condition of readily accessible service panel components, note the presence of GFCIs, AFCIs, smoke alarms and check the operation of representative outlets, switches, fixtures and other devices. ",
  },
  {
    image: Wall,
    textFront: "Walls, Ceilings, & Floors",
    textBack: "Inspectors check for leaning, cracked, or bowed walls, all of which may be signs of defects in the foundation or underlying structure of the home. Inspectors will also look for popping nail heads or drywall tape tears. Additionally, inspectors look for signs of moisture.  Termite damage is also on an inspector’s radar; peeling or pitted paint may indicate termite damage underneath. Inspectors examine ceilings for cracks that may indicate structural problems as well as any signs that moisture is getting into the ceiling from the attic or rooms above.  Sloping, uneven floors may mean the structure underneath is damaged due to ground settling, moisture, or termites. Inspectors look closely at all floors to make certain there are no indications of serious problems",
  },
  {
    image: Wind,
    textFront: "Exterior",
    textBack: "We inspect visible siding and trim, windows, doors, garages, porches, decks, stairs, and railings. We assess the elements for proper construction and function; looking for damage, missing components or other conditions that might lead to infiltration or functional concerns. Inspectors go through your home to check proper air sealing. They look for air gaps along windows, walls, and doors as well as openings near electrical wiring, HVAC system connections, and other places. Identifying and closing these gaps will help make your home more energy efficient.",
  },
  {
    image: Basement,
    textFront: "Interior",
    textBack: "What we inspect: visible areas of all walls, ceilings, stairways, representative windows and doors, and attic areas for signs of leakage and damage, sagging or other structural concerns. Windows will be operated to determine function. In accessible attics, besides assessing structural components, we will note insulation and ventilation conditions. ",
  },
  {
    image: Basement,
    textFront: "Basement & Foundation",
    textBack: "Basements are often a source of excess moisture and leaks, especially in unfinished basements. Visible load-bearing framing components, foundation walls, slabs, piers and columns and accessible structural components will be assessed for function and presence of damage, decay or defects. past flooding and water damage, and moisture due to poor ventilation or insulation water penetration at below grade areas",
  },
  {
    image: Drainage,
    textFront: "Grading & Drainage",
    textBack: "Ideally your land should slope away from the foundation of your home. A failure in any of the elements of your homes drainage system can lead to major structural damage. Faulty gutters or grading that doesn’t have the appropriate fall away from the structure will lead to water pooling around the foundation which could lead to foundation damage in the long-term.",
  },
  {
    image: Roof,
    textFront: "Roof, Flashings, & Trim",
    textBack: 
    " We assess the condition of visible roof covering materials, (shingles), flashings at roof penetrations and valleys, skylights, chimneys, gutters and downspouts for proper function, looking for evidence of leakage or worn, damaged, or missing components. We also utilize drone technology when unable to safely access the roof to provide a full evaluation.",
  },
  {
    image: Gutter,
    textFront: "Gutters & Downspouts",
    textBack: "A no-good gutter can mean anything from one that just needs a bit of cleaning to one that is completely structurally unsound. Without a proper gutter water carelessly rolls off the roof and can easily make its way under the shingles or into the siding. The longer it sits there the more damage it will do and in the long-term it can cause some major issues.",
  },
  {
    image: HeatCool,
    textFront: "Heating & Cooling",
    textBack: " Visible components of the central AC or heat pump system including condensers and air handlers, and the distribution ductwork. We assess the function and condition of the accessible indoor/ outdoor components. ",
  },
  {
    image: Plumb,
    textFront: "Interior Plumbing System",
    textBack: "We inspect visible water supply piping, distribution piping, waste system piping, water heaters and plumbing fixtures. We check plumbing fixtures and built-in appliances looking for water pressure or drainage issues and visible signs of leaks. Also includes inspection of the physical condition and operation of piping to asses flow, drainage and leakage. ",
  },
  {
    image: Attic,
    textFront: "Attic & Visible Insulation",
    textBack: " A number of structural issues are discovered in the attic and crawl spaces. Damaged (cracked or loose) roof rafters, floor joists and leaking foundations are revealed when these spaces are inspected. The condition of insulation or inadequate ventilation can be discovered inspecting these spaces.",
  },
];

// export var services = [
//   {
//     image: Plug,
//     text: "Electrical Panels & Breakers",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Wall,
//     text: "Walls, Ceilings, & Floors",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Wind,
//     text: "Windows & Doors",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Basement,
//     text: "Basement & Foundation",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Drainage,
//     text: "Grading & Drainage",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Roof,
//     text: "Roof, Flashings, & Trim",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Gutter,
//     text: "Gutters & Downspouts",
//   },
//   {
//     image: HeatCool,
//     text: "Heating & Cooling",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Plumb,
//     text: "Interior Plumbing System",
//   },
//   {
//     image: Attic,
//     text: "Attic & Visible Insulation",
//   },
// ];

// export var newServices = [
//   {
//     id: 1,
//     title: "TOWNHOME, MANUFACTURED HOME, DUPLEX, MULTIPLEX INSPECTION",
//     text: "There are many aspects of condominiums, townhomes, manufactured and mobile homes, duplexes and multiplexes that differ from a permanent residence. Similar to a full home inspection, the home inspector reviews all visual aspects of all major systems specific to these types of homes.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 2,
//     title: "PRE-LISTING INSPECTION",
//     text: "A WIN pre-listing home inspection provides you with comprehensive information on the current condition of your home and includes recommendations for property repairs and enhancements to improve the home’s value and marketability.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 3,
//     title: "PRE-OFFER INSPECTION ",
//     text: "More common in competitive real estate markets with multiple offers, this preliminary, information-only home inspection evaluates a home’s major systems and any potential issues, giving home buyers the information to make an informed decision on whether to place an offer on a property.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 4,
//     title: "NEW CONSTRUCTION INSPECTION",
//     text: "Buying a newly constructed home gives you the opportunity to pick the colors, finishes, and other details that truly make a house your own. But how can you be sure that the quality of your new home isn’t only skin deep? New construction inspections from WIN monitor the home building process at critical building stages to verify that the construction is sound and provides you with the information you need to make informed decisions about your new home.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 5,
//     title: "LIGHT COMMERCIAL INSPECTION",
//     text: "Commercial property inspections are a growing portion of the inspection industry. Evaluation of acommercial property has many of the same attributes as a residential home inspection. Our qualified inspectors will evaluate the property under the guidance of the nationally accepted Standards of Practice for Commercial Buildings.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 6,
//     title: "WOOD DESTROYING ORGANISMS / INSECTS (WDO/WDI) INSPECTION",
//     text: "WIN's wood destroying organism/insect inspection can be performed at the same time as one of our other inspections, or on its own, so you'll know if termites, ants, dry rot, or another type of destructive organism has worked its way into your house, and your home inspector will provide you with advice on how to handle the problem.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 7,
//     title: "RADON TESTING",
//     text: "WIN Home Inspection provides radon testing so you will have peace of mind regarding the safety of your home.",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 8,
//     title: "IR THERMOGRAPHY",
//     text: "An Infrared (IR) thermal scan can help find anomalies that may otherwise remain hidden in walls, floors and ceilings.",
//   },
// ];

// export var prices = [
//   {
//     id: 1,
//     service: "Average Single Family Home (max 4 bed, 2 bath)",
//     secondaryText: "up to 2000 sq ft.",
//     price: "$425.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 2,
//     service: "Large Single Family Home, (max 5 bed, 4 bath) ",
//     price: "$500.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 3,
//     service: "Larger Single Family Home",
//     price: "schedule for price quote",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 4,
//     service: "Condo / Townhouse",
//     price: "$375.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 5,
//     service: "Two-family home",
//     price: "$550.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 6,
//     service: "Three-Four Family Home",
//     price: "$650.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 7,
//     service: "Radon gas test",
//     price: "$125.00 ",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 8,
//     service: "Radon Test Only (No Home Inspection)",
//     price: "$150.00",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 9,
//     service: "House is over 75 years old additional fee ",
//     price: "$75.00",
//   },
// ];

// export var priceCard = [
//   {
//     id: 1,
//     summary: "(Up to 2,500 sq. ft.) Single-family homes/townhomes",
//     price: "$395",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 2,
//     summary: "Condominiums",
//     price: "$325",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 3,
//     summary: "*Properties over 2,500 sq. ft.",
//     price: "request a free quote today!",
//   },
// ];

// export var bundlePrice = [
//   {
//     id: 1,
//     summary: "Home Inspection Radon Testing Termite",
//     price: "$540",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 1,
//     summary: "Radon Testing",
//     secondaryText: "w/ Home Inspection:",
//     price: "$125",
//     secondaryPrice: "$100",
//   },
//   {
//     id: 2,
//     summary: "Termite testing",
//     secondaryText: "w/ Home Inspection:",
//     price: "$110",
//     secondaryPrice: "$90",
//   },
// ];
